http://www.edcocu.com/privacy-policy

Money Market Savings
Certificates of Deposit (CDs)
Money Market Savings
Certificates of Deposit (CDs)
Privacy Policy
We understand and are committed to protecting the privacy of our members. Therefore, we are committed to maintaining the confidentiality of each member’s financial records, consistent with state and federal laws. This Privacy Policy sets forth our policies regarding our use and protection of your financial information.
Section I: Collection and Use of Information
During the course of business, we collect the information you provide to us as well as information available from public records and credit reports. We use the information about you to administer your records and accounts, to process your transactions, to assist us in developing new products and services, to aid you in learning more about our products and services, and to fulfill any legal and regulatory requirements.
We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:
Information we receive from you on applications or other forms
Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others
Information obtained by verifying representations made by you
Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency
Section II: Sharing Information with Third Parties
We may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to companies that perform services on our behalf, such as check-printing companies, or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. Generally, we share your nonpublic personal information with non-affiliated third parties to complete transactions and maintain accounts and related records (such as data processing transactions and records). We may also share information with select nonaffiliated third parties.
If you request or authorize it
When the information is provided to help complete a transaction initiated by you
When the information is provided to a consumer reporting agency in accordance with the Fair Credit Reporting Act
When the disclosure otherwise is lawfully required or permitted
At times we may enter into agreements with other businesses to provide support or services to us or for one or more of our products, such as check-printing. Under certain circumstances we may also enter into joint marketing agreements with other financial institutions. Before entering into relationships with such entities, we require them to agree to safeguard our members’ information and to comply with all applicable privacy laws.
Please be assured that we do not provide account information or personal information to nonaffiliated third parties for the purpose of independent telemarketing or direct mail marketing of any products or services of those parties.
Section III: Information Sharing in the Event of Termination of Membership
If you decide to terminate your membership or become an inactive member, we will adhere to the privacy policies and practices as described in this notice.
Section IV: Security of Information
We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. Our employees access information about you when needed to administer your accounts, to provide requested services, or in response to a legally valid outside request or order (such as a subpoena).
Our employees may also access information to exercise our rights under the law or pursuant to any agreement with you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information. We also continually update and assess our systems to improve our technology for protecting information.
Section V: Accuracy of Information
We strive to ensure that our records contain accurate information about you. If you see any inaccuracies in your statements, please call 800-234-5628. We will promptly investigate and make any necessary changes to update your records.
Section VI: What Members Can do to Help
FPCU is committed to protecting the privacy of our members. Members can help by following these simple guidelines:
Protect your account numbers, card numbers, PINs and Passwords. Never keep your PIN with your ATM, Debit or Credit card(s). Doing so could provide free access to your accounts if these cards are lost or stolen.
Use caution when disclosing your account number, social security numbers, etc. to other persons.
Do not send account numbers, social security numbers, etc. over unsecured e-mail.
Do not save your passwords or Pins on your computer.
Keep your information with us current. It is important that we have current information on how to reach you. If we detect potentially fraudulent or unauthorized activity or use of an account, we will attempt to contact you immediately. If your address or phone number changes, please let us know.
Section VII: Changes to Our Policy
We reserve the right to revise our privacy policy as our business needs change or as the law requires. If we revise our policy, we will provide our active members with copies of our new policies at that time.
Online Supplement: About Online Privacy
Web Access: Information we collect
When you visit our site we log the time, date, how you arrived, where you went, and where you are connecting from. We use this information primarily to measure traffic on our site, popular pages, and system capacity. We do not currently use this information for marketing purposes, and do not provide it to any third party.
Web Access: Cookies
In order to provide certain web-based services and make your online experience more personalized, we sometimes place "cookies" on your computer. A "cookie" is a very small piece of information stored on your local computer so it can later be read back by our server. This is useful for having the browser remember some specific information and shortening download times or personalizing your content. FPCU currently uses cookies for PlusNet.
FPCU does not:
Use cookies to identify you or determine your e-mail address
Give or share cookie information with any other companies or institutions
For more detailed information on cookies, click on http://www.cookiecentral.com/.
Web Access: PlusNet
When you log in to PlusNet, we verify your account number and PIN on our host system to protect your account. Your PIN is not available to credit union employees.
We gather and analyze transaction data for diagnostics and capacity planning.
Transactions are encrypted using 128-bit SSL encryption protocol. The SSL security protocol provides data encryption, server authentication, message integrity, and optional client authentication for a TCP/IP connection. SSL is built into all major browsers and web serve
Our Locations
West Des Moines Office
515.224.1222
515.224.1222
1831 25th Street
West Des Moines,
Des Moines,
Des Moines,
Des Moines,
IA 50312
Routing Number: 273074261  |  Wire Instructions
Contact Us: 1-800-234-5628 1-800-234-5628  |  Email
Debit Cards Lost/Stolen: 1-800-383-80001-800-383-8000
Debit Cards Blocked/Denied Transactions: 1-866-508-26931-866-508-2693
Credit Card Issues: 1-866-570-12381-866-570-1238
© 2020 Financial Plus Credit Union. All rights reserved.
Privacy
Sitemap
Get Adobe Acrobat Reader
© 2020 Financial Plus Credit Union. All rights reserved.
